batesexterminating.com 2017-03-11

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
This website is provided by Bates Exterminating
Bates Exterminating recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal and financial
information. We have instituted strict policies and security measures to protect information we may
collect from you. When you register online with Bates Exterminating or use our online bill paying or
credit card provisions, you give us your consent to process and use your personal data in
accordance with this online Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all users of this Bates
Exterminating website.
What                     Information                     Bates                   Exterminating                     Collects
Bates Exterminating collects personal information from visitors to the website who voluntarily submit their information when
registering on the website or using the online store. We also collect non-personally identifying information such as IP
addresses, and we use cookies (see more below) so we can improve our services and enhance your Bates Exterminating
experience. Bates Exterminating does not collect personally identifiable information from anyone that it knows is under the
age of eighteen. If you are under eighteen, please ask your parents to register and/or use the online store. Please do not
submit any personal details if you are under eighteen years of age.
How              Bates             Exterminating             Uses            Information             You             Provide
If you give us your personal information, we may use this information to register you with our website, to administer our
website services, and/or to process any orders you may place online. We will send you announcements or communications
by e-mail only if you give us your permission to do so. You may opt out of receiving such communications by visiting our
website and following the appropriate instructions. Otherwise, we use your information only to review our performance and
to improve our services to you, or to communicate with you about your order if you have placed an online order.
Does                  Bates         Exterminating         Share        Your         Information        With         Others?
Bates Exterminating does not sell, rent or disclose our client's names, addresses, e-mail addresses or other personal
information to any non-Bates Exterminating entity. Bates Exterminating may share client information within the Bates
Exterminating organization, including other commonly-owned brands, so that you may be informed of other products that
may be of interest to you. Further, in order to maintain our website and provide our client communications, Bates
Exterminating contracts with selected third parties. As necessary, your personal information may be processed by these
third parties, solely for the purpose of assisting Bates Exterminating in these endeavors and subject to strict contractual
confidentiality obligations. We do not otherwise disclose your information to third parties, unless required by law or in
connection with a legal claim or proceeding. If Bates Exterminating is acquired by or merges with another entity, information
about Bates Exterminating clients and website users may be made available to that other entity.
Security
Bates Exterminating uses appropriate security measures to protect the information you give us. However, while we take all
reasonable steps to protect your personal information, you accept that no Internet data transmission can be guaranteed to
be secure from access by unintended recipients and agree that Bates Exterminating is not responsible for any breach of
security unless this is due to our negligence.
About                                                                                                               Cookies
Cookies are small text files a web server can send through your computer's browser to your company's hard drive to assist
with record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to ascertain which web pages are visited and how often, to make our web
site more user friendly, and to give you a better experience when you return to the website. For example, cookies allow us to
save your password so you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our site. Most web browsers automatically accept
cookies, but you do not have to accept them. To disable cookies, you should access the "help" tab on your browser or read

the information that came with your browser software. However, your visit to our website will be significantly enhanced if
cookies are not disabled.
Acceptance                  of               Privacy                Policy                 and                 Modifications
By accessing and using the Bates Exterminating website, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal
and non-personally identifying information as described in this Privacy Policy. Bates Exterminating reserves the right
occasionally to make changes to its Privacy Policy or practices from time to time. You should therefore review this webpage
occasionally and at least each time you use the online shop to get updated information. We will notify you of any changes in
our Privacy Policy by posting the modifications on our website. Your continued use of this website following the posting of
any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.
Contact Us
If you have any comments or queries regarding our Privacy Policy, please call or write to us at the following address:
Bates Exterminating
Mailing Address
1311 Commerce Lane, Suite #16
Jupiter, Florida 33458
Phone: 561-746-2651
Toll Free: 800-774-2651
